In our first clip we're going to actually talk about the construction of the mirrors.
They're approximately 1 foot square.
They're unbreakable, and one of the reasons being unbreakable is I have the boxers stand about where they can punch the mirror and then step about a half a foot back.
So too many times they'll be stepping in and they'll be actually hitting the mirror, which is really not what we want to do.
But just in case they do, we don't want them to break.
The reason we've got them cut down to about a foot square is we used to use a full-length mirror, and some of the boxers still use the full-length mirrors in their shadowboxing, etcetera, but that doesn't give you the actual circumference of your head of a target-type position.
Even with a full length mirror if you take a magic marker and draw a circle around it you'll get the effect of a target, but this gives you that much more.
Once you duck down you're out of the mirror, and that's the best thing about having just the 1 foot mirror.
That way you're limited to just that one foot.
Once you're out of there, you're out of that mirror.